Baby Elephant Hana-chan
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
My canary pet, Piko-chan, was very agitated, so I decided to check in our house.
Then I saw our gas stove had gas leaking.
That must have been very dangerous!
it could have burst!
Right, but our lives were saved thanks to my Piko-chan.
Speaking of which, our dog Mook once caught a robber.
Ain't that great?
Really?
My Mook is a very reliable dog.
Our Persian cat once retrieved my mum's lost ruby ring worth ¥1,000,000.
Animals are so lovely.
They love you back with interest added, if you love them.
I'm leaving.
I too want an pet animal to catch robber and warn me about gas leakage.
I want to surprise all by buying an exquisite animal like a Lion or an Elephant.
Be reasonable!
You do know that your mum don't like any animals, don't you?
Yes, but...
I say, give it up!
But you'll come up with something, if it's for me.
Badger Robot from the future, Doraemon-kun!
You're flattering me!
Wild Pet House!
You can get animals using this?
Just wait and see for yourself!
There's a green plain over there!
Come on! Let's go!
Wow!
It's so vast!
Where are we?
It's an African Savanna.
It seems little different than an Anywhere Door.
Yes, it is...
It's a lion! Let's run!
We are saved!
I was so scared for life!
What are you saying now? You wanted to get a lion then.
Don't wanna! No need Lion anymore!
I wanna get some other animal.
If you turn the dial around, you may find the animal you prefer.
It's a Giraffe!
A Hippo.
I'm so disappointed.
An elephant.
That's it! An elephant!
Turn the dial around.
A baby Elephant! How cute!
Hope it's not abandoned.
Usually, baby Elephants are surrounded by their mother and Elephants in their group.
Maybe they were shot by the poachers, and got lost.
I hope it's mother is okay.
This baby Elephant looks not well.
It must be hungry, it needs milk.
Mum, gimme milk!
I managed to get a glass of milk.
I'll take care of that!
Big Light!
I knew you'd do something!
Drink up!
Why aren't you drinking?
Maybe it doesn't like a cow's milk!
No way!
It'll die if it doesn't drink it up.
I'll try feeding it the Momotaro Dumplings.
It's, for-all animal food.
It started drinking.
Aren't you happy, Young Elephant?
It's tickling me!
Come here, Hana-chan!
Come on!
How cute!
Yay!
Are you still up, Nobita-kun?
You'll be late for school if you don't fall asleep now.
Say, Doraemon. I wonder how's Hana-chan doing and what if it went somewhere else?
Don't worry, the door connects automatically to wherever Hana-chan is.
It's Hana-chan's scream!
It's a pack of Hyenas.
Even though it's an Elephant, it's but a baby, so it's still no mach for the pack of wolves...
Let's go home!
We are safe now.
Tonight let's sleep together!
Remember, we must send it back to Africa tomorrow morning...
Why not? Sure.
Hana-chan!
Hey, Nobita!
You seem to be enjoying something!
Do you have some good news?
Cute Hana-chan is waiting for me! I must go1
Wait for me, Hana-chan!
Good boy!
Stop!
It's an herd of Elephants...
It must be the mother of Hana-chan!
Hurry! Heave ho!
Say, Nobita-kun. We must return Hana-chan to it's mother.
It can't be with you forever.
Japan is too packed and cold.
It might fall sick if we don't return it quickly...
Hana-chan want to live with its mother, in a vast, windy continent like Africa.
Nobita, run an errand for me!
Okay, mum.
Return Hana-chan to Africa!
Stop.
Nobita, there's list of things to buy and money inside this bag.
What was that?
Nothing really.
Hana-chan that Nobita got is...
Why are you in such a hurry, Nobita?
Hana-chan!
Hana-chan is an Elephant?
Let's go and find out!
What's going on?
What's an elephant doing here?
No way!
Wait up, Hana-chan!
Hey, stop!
Doraemon, take out your Bamboo 'Copter!
Go, Hana-chan, your mother is waiting for you!
Now, go!
Let's return home!